<resources>
    <string name="jogging">
        \t \t \t  <b>1. Warm-up exercises: Jogging</b>
        \n
        \n
        \t \t A good warm up jog can help to prepare a body by waking it up and steadily raising the heart rate. It also helps to increase the effectiveness of stretching.
        \n
        \t \t Jogging about 3-5 laps around the netball court should be sufficient for the beginning of the warmup.
        \n
        \n
        \n
        \t \t \t <b>2. Warm-up exercises: Stretching</b>
        \n
        \n
        \t \t Once a body has been prepared and woken up by jogging, stretching should be the next one on the exercise list.
        \n
        \t \t It is the best exercise for preventing injuries and increasing the range of movement.
        \n
        \t \t There are a few muscle groups that netball players should especially focus on:
        \n
        \n
        \n
        \t \t \t <b>1) Legs</b>
        \n
        \t \t Netball sessions involve a lot of running, so legs have to be sufficiently prepared. Some of the legs exercises that the players can perform are:
        \n
        \n
        \t \t - \t <b>Toe Touches</b> – from a standing position, bend and touch your toes. Do not you’re your knees. Hold for 20 seconds and repeat a few times.
        \n \n
        \t \t - \t <b>Hurdler Stretch</b> – tuck your right leg behind you and reach for your toe in front for 10 seconds. Switch and repeat with the other leg.
        \n \n
        \t \t - <b>\t The Pretzel</b> – it is a good exercise for stretching both legs and back. Sit down, extend your left leg and cross right leg over the top with your knee up. Cross your body using your left arm and turn your body to the right side. Hold it for 10 seconds and repeat on the other side.
        \n \n
        \t \t - \t <b>Front Squad</b> – it is a good exercise for stretching groin area. Do a squat to the balls of your feet with your legs spread apart. Place arms on the ground in front of you. Lean forward, keep your elbows to the inside of your knees and hold it for 20 seconds.
        \n \n
        \t \t - \t <b>Calf Stretches</b> – Place your toes on the wall or fence at an upward angle and hold it for 20 seconds. Do it for each calf separately. After completion, point each toe for 5-10 seconds.
        \n \n \n
        \t \t \t <b>2) Upper Body and Arms</b>
        \n
        \t \t Playing netball involves an intensive arm movement and the need for mobility, so it’s really important to properly warm them up. Exercises include:
        \n \n
        \t \t - \t Lay on the ground, curl your knees into your chest and hold it for 10 seconds.
        \n \n
        \t \t - \t In a standing position, lean to your left side and extend your right arm. Hold it for 20 seconds, switch and repeat with the other side.
        \n \n
        \t \t - \t Drop your left arm behind your head and gently pull on a left elbow using your right hand. Hold it for 15 seconds and repeat with the other arm.
        \n \n
        \t \t - \t Cross your left arm across your chest and use your right arm to pull it at the elbow. Hold it for 10 seconds and repeat with your other arm.
        \n \n
        \t \t - \t Let your head hang, slowly moving it from side to side for 15 seconds.
        \n
        \n \n To maintain the good feeling of a warmed-up body, stay active and keep your muscles warm.
        \n
        \t \t - \t Do 25 Star Jumps
        \n \n
        \t \t - \t To practice defence manoeuvres while keeping your body nice and warm, face one of the sidelines and do side shuffle to the half court line while waving your arms.
        \n \n Take a moment before your netball session, go over the strategy and prepare yourself mentally.
        \n \n \n
        \t \t No matter the outcome of the game, you do this to enjoy yourself, so HAVE FUN!
        \n \n
        \t \t After the session/game, do some stretching exercises mentioned above to cool down and relax your body.
        \n \n \n
        \t \t <b>Enjoy your well-deserved rest!</b>




 </string>
    <string name="app_name">

    </string>
</resources>